Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - P
        - Pool - Dance it down, 1983; SR-28042; Pool (Box 392)
        - Pool-Pah - The flasher, 1973; SR-28043; Pool-Pah (Box 392)
          Catalog # GBS-1008; A-side Matrix # GBS1008A-4
          Greene Bottle Records, Inc.
        - Pooley, Ian - What's your number, 1998; SR-28044; Pooley, Ian (Box 392)
          Catalog # VVR5003316; A-side Matrix # WR5003316
          V2 Records
          London
        - Poor Righteous Teachers - Conscious style, 1996; SR-28045; Poor Righteous Teachers; KRS-One (Box 392)
          Catalog # PRO-7460-ADV; A-side Matrix # PA-696 PRO-7460-0 A
        - Poor Righteous Teachers - Conscious style, 1996; SR-28046; Poor Righteous Teachers; KRS-One (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28047. 2 copies.
        - Poor Righteous Teachers - Conscious style, 1996; SR-28047; Poor Righteous Teachers; KRS-One (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28046. 2 copies.
        - Poor Righteous Teachers - Nobody Move; Da Rill Shit, 1993; SR-28048; Poor Righteous Teachers (Box 392)
          Catalog # PRO-7404-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7404-A
        - Poorsah - Go right up in day; Up in day jam, 1990; SR-28049; Poorsah (Box 392)
          Catalog # TRIN 008; A-side Matrix # GS 2740 A TRIN-008-A
          Trindisc
          Brixton, London
        - Pop Da Brown Hornet - Black on black crime, 1996; SR-28050; Pop Da Brown Hornet (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28051. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SMOKE002LP; A-side Matrix # BOBC-1-A SMOKE 002A
          Smoke Records
        - Pop Da Brown Hornet - Black on black crime, 1996; SR-28051; Pop Da Brown Hornet (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28050. 2 copies.
        - Pop, Iggy - Special rock club versions from the Iggy Pop album party, 1981; SR-28052; Pop, Iggy (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28053. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-115; A-side Matrix # T SP-115-SA-CT3
        - Pop, Iggy - Special rock club versions from the Iggy Pop album party, 1981; SR-28053; Pop, Iggy (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28052. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-115; A-side Matrix # T SP-115-SA-CT4
        - Pop, Iggy - Motor inn, 2003; SR-28054; Pop, Iggy; Feedom; Peaches (Box 392)
          Catalog # 7087 6 18170 1 0; A-side Matrix # 7087 6 18170 1 0 B RE 2
          Virgin Records America, Inc.
        - Pop Megga - Ghetto news, 1996; SR-28055; Pop Megga (Box 392)
          Catalog # PRO-7452-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7452-O-A
        - Pop Will Eat Itself - X Y & Zee, 1991; SR-28056; Pop Will Eat Itself (Box 392)
          Catalog # PT44246; A-side Matrix # B PT-44246-B
        - Pop Will Eat Itself - Dance of the mad, 1990; SR-28057; Pop Will Eat Itself (Box 392)
          Catalog # PT44024; A-side Matrix # PT 44024 A-1U-1-1
        - Pop Will Eat Itself - Touched by the hand of Cicciolina (replay), 1990; SR-28058; Pop Will Eat Itself (Box 392)
          Catalog # PT43738; A-side Matrix # PT43738A-1
        - Poppa Bear Kool Breez - Lighter, 1996; SR-28059; Poppa Bear Kool Breez (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28060. 2 copies.
          Catalog # RWK 103; A-side Matrix # RWK-103-1A2
          Rawkus Entertainment
        - Poppa Bear Kool Breez - Lighter, 1996; SR-28060; Poppa Bear Kool Breez (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28059. 2 copies.
        - Poppa Bear Kool Breez - Lighter, 1996; SR-28061; Poppa Bear Kool Breez (Box 392)
        - Poppa Doo - Walk like a play-ya, 1994; SR-28062; Poppa Doo (Box 392)
          Catalog # 01624 15517-1; A-side Matrix # 01624-15517-1-A
          Critique
        - Poppa Ron Love - I'm a girl watcher, 1989; SR-28063; Poppa Ron Love (Box 392)
          Catalog # 44-68783; A-side Matrix # XSS-68783A-1A
        - Popu, Nandu - All'Infiernu; Mamma li turchi, 1993; SR-28064; Popu, Nandu (Box 392)
          Catalog # CVX 659121-6; A-side Matrix # 37 659121 20 1A1
        - Porn Kings - Amour (Disc one), 1997; SR-28065; Porn Kings (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28066. Double album.
          Catalog # INT 8 84065 6; A-side Matrix # INT 884 065 6 - A1
          Maddog
        - Porn Kings - Amour (Disc two), 1997; SR-28066; Porn Kings (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28065. Double album.
          Catalog # INT 8 84065 6; A-side Matrix # 33 UPM INT 884 065 6 - C1
        - O Porradão Do Funk - Agitando as galeras, 1995; SR-25090; O Porradão Do Funk (Box 392)
          Catalog # OXX-1082-2; A-side Matrix # JB-1-114219-A
          Paradoxx Music
          Rio de Janeiro, Brazil
        - Porter, Marquise - Lobster tailz, 2004; SR-28067; Porter, Marquise (Box 392)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # 9695 - LOBSTER - 1 (A) S - 56508
          Nasty North
        - Portishead - Portishead (Disc one), 1997; SR-28068; Portishead (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28069. Double album.
          Catalog # PORT LP PRO; A-side Matrix # PORT LP PRO A1
          Go! Beat
        - Portishead - Portishead (Disc two), 1997; SR-28069; Portishead (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28068. Double album.
          Catalog # PORT LP PRO; A-side Matrix # PORT LP PRO C1
        - Poser - Tempo Soca, 1979; SR-28070; Poser (Box 392)
          Catalog # SM 038; A-side Matrix # SM-038-A
          Charlie's Records
        - Positive Black Souls - Boul fale, 1995; SR-38071; Positive Black Souls (Box 392)
          Catalog # 12 MNG 829DJ; A-side Matrix # 12+MNG+829+DJ+A EX
        - Positive Choice - Super sonic stereophonic funk, 1980; SR-38072; Positive Choice (Box 392)
          Catalog # DSC 142; A-side Matrix # T1 DSC-142-SA-2 CTH
          Buddah Records
        - Positive Force - We got the funk, 1979; SR-28073; Positive Force (Box 392)
          Catalog # TU-452; A-side Matrix # TU-134-GM-1
          Turbo Records
        - Positive Force - Especially for you, 1980; SR-28074; Positive Force (Box 392)
          Catalog # SH 552; A-side Matrix # VID-180X
          Sugar Hill Records
        - Positive K - Night shift, 1991; SR-28075; Positive K (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28076. 2 copies.
          Catalog # POSK1; A-side Matrix # POS K 1 A AATB
          Creative Control Records
        - Positive K - Night shift, 1991; SR-28076; Positive K (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28075. 2 copies.
        - Positive K - Supreme alphabet, 2001; SR-28077; Positive K (Box 392)
          Catalog # POSK02V; A-side Matrix # POSK02-V-A
        - Positive K - Ain't no crime, 1993; SR-28078; Positive K (Box 392)
          Catalog # PR12 6780-1; A-side Matrix # PR12 6780 -1AS AS
        - Positive K - Black cinderella, 1996; SR-28079; Positive K (Box 392)
          Catalog # 80002; A-side Matrix # 80002-1-A
          PosK Records
        - Positive K - Quarter gram pam, 1987; SR-28080; Positive K (Box 392)
          Catalog # FPM 2939; A-side Matrix # FPM 2939A SUNSHINE-FRANK
          First Priority Music
        - Positive K - Quarter gram pam, 1987; SR-28081; Positive K (Box 392)
        - Positive K - I got a man, 1993; SR-28082; Positive K (Box 392)
          Catalog # PR12 6764-1; A-side Matrix # PR-12-6764-1AS HS
        - Positive K - I got a man, 1993; SR-28083; Positive K (Box 392)
        - Positive K - Ain't no crime, 1993; SR-28084; Positive K (Box 392)
          Catalog # PR12 6780-1; A-side Matrix # PR12 6780 -1AS HS
        - Positive K - I got a man; Night shift, 1992; SR-28085; Positive K (Box 392)
          Catalog # 422-864 305-1 DJ; A-side Matrix # 422-864-305-1-AS/SP
        - Positive K - The skills dat pay da bills (disc two), 1992; SR-28086; Positive K (Box 392)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # POSITNEK-C
        - Positive K - The skills dat pay da bills, 1992; SR-28087; Positive K (Box 392)
          Catalog # 314-514 057-1ADV; A-side Matrix # 314-514-057-1-BSP1 DMM REI SP 1 -1
        - Positive K - Step up front, 1988; SR-28088; Positive K (Box 392)
          Catalog # 0-96621; A-side Matrix # CSB STDM-55733-55734-55735-5 F/W
        - Positive K - A good combination; I'm not having it, 1989; SR-28089; Positive K; MC Lyte (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28090. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DMD 1357; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-57205-57214-1 1-1
        - Positive K - A good combination; I'm not having it, 1989; SR-28090; Positive K; MC Lyte (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28089. 2 copies.
        - Positive K - Night shift, 1991; SR-28091; Positive K (Box 392)
        - Positive Noise - Positive negative, 1982; SR-28092; Positive Noise (Box 393)
          Catalog # STAT 812; A-side Matrix # STAT 812 A1
          Statik Records
        - Positive Noise - When lightning strikes, 1983; SR-28093; Positive Noise (Box 393)
          Catalog # TAK 8-12; A-side Matrix # TAK 812 A-1U-1-1
        - Positively Black - Think like ya enemy, 1988; SR-28094; Positively Black; Prince Kharique (Box 393)
          Catalog # TR-158; A-side Matrix # CSB TR12"-158A F/W
          Trumpet
          Fanwood, New Jersey
        - Positively Black - Escape from reality, 1989; SR-28095; Positively Black (Box 393)
          Catalog # FMS 62339; A-side Matrix # FMS-62339A-RE2
        - Posse Mente Zulu - Revolusom parte 1, 1994; SR-28096; Posse Mente Zulu (Box 393)
          Catalog # PMZ 01; A-side Matrix # PMZ01-A
          Raízes Discos Ltda.
        - Posse NFX - Black or ya white, 1991; SR-28097; Posse NFX (Box 393)
          Catalog # 01624 15478-1; A-side Matrix # 0162415478-1-A
          Woburn, Massachusetts
        - Possessione - II posto dove vivo, 1993; SR-28098; Possessione (Box 393)
          Catalog # 659328 6; A-side Matrix # 37 659328 20 1A1
          San Isidro
          Holland
        - Postmen - Corrosion, 1998; SR-28099; Postmen (Box 393)
          Catalog # VVR5003986; A-side Matrix # 08 40142 20 1A1
          V2
        - Postaboy - Wind it up, 2004; SR-28100; Postaboy (Box 393)
          Catalog # UNIR 21196-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-21196-1-REI
        - Potna Deuce - Dat's my potna, 1994; SR-28101; Potna Deuce (Box 393)
          Catalog # PRO-7419-0-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7419-0A AATB
        - Potter, Andrew Scott - N.Y. to L.A.: coasting, 1980; SR-28102; Potter, Andrew Scott; Tillman, David (Box 393)
          Catalog # POET 222; A-side Matrix # POET-222-A
          Poet Records
        - Pound Puppy D.J.'s - Weed head, 1993; SR-28103; Pound Puppy D.J.'s; Lick'em Down Boyz (Box 393)
          Catalog # MVP 1241; A-side Matrix # 124-A
          MVP Records
          Palm Beach, Florida
        - Poussez! - Leave that boy alone!; Don't stop, keep movin', 1980; SR-28104; Poussez! (Box 393)
          Catalog # SPV 33; A-side Matrix # SPV 33A-1A
          Vanguard Disco
        - P.O.V. - Anutha luv, 1993; SR-28105; P.O.V. (Box 393)
          In same jacket as # SR-28106. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRO-A-6003; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-6003 SR-1
          Giant Records
        - P.O.V. - Anutha luv, 1993; SR-28106; P.O.V. (Box 393)
          In same jacket as # SR-28105. 2 copies.
        - Pōvi ‎ - Dragonflies, 1999; SR-28107; Pōvi ‎ (Box 393)
          Catalog # 0 6700 33099 1 2; A-side Matrix # p/m RCE 0-6700-33099-1A
          Nettwerk America
        - Powell, Doc - Give it up, 1987; SR-28108; Powell, Doc (Box 393)
          Catalog # 870 105-1; A-side Matrix # 870-105-1-AS-SP4
        - Powell, Jesse - Gloria, 1996; SR-28109; Powell, Jesse (Box 393)
          Catalog # LSJ12 55209; A-side Matrix # LSJ-12620-BG1 REV UORGE
          Silas Records
        - Powell, Jesse - Gloria, 1996; SR-28110; Powell, Jesse (Box 393)
        - Powell, Jesse - All I need, 1996; SR-28111; Powell, Jesse (Box 393)
          In same jacket as # SR-28112. Different discs.
          Catalog # LSJ12-55181; A-side Matrix # LSJ-12513
        - Powell, Jesse - All I need, 1996; SR-28112; Powell, Jesse (Box 393)
          In same jacket as # SR-28111. Different discs.
          Catalog # LSJ8P-3664; A-side Matrix # (LSJ8P-3664-A) LSJ-12507
        - Powell, Jesse - 'Bout It, 'Bout It (Remix), 1999; SR-28113; Powell, Jesse (Box 393)
          Catalog # LSJ8P4415; A-side Matrix # OASIS DISC MASTERING LSJ 13543 (Side A)
        - Powell, Jesse - I wasn't with it, 1998; SR-28114; Powell, Jesse (Box 393)
          Catalog # LSJ8P-4259; A-side Matrix # OASIS DISC MASTERING LSJ 13238 (SIDE ONE)
        - Powell, Jesse - I like it, 1996; SR-28115; Powell, Jesse (Box 393)
          Catalog # LSJ8P-3908; A-side Matrix # OASIS DISC MASTERING #LSJ12727-A
        - Powell, Jesse - Gloria, 1996; SR-28116; Powell, Jesse (Box 393)
          Catalog # LSJ8P 3802; A-side Matrix # LSJ-12624-BG1
        - Power - Power, 1982; SR-28117; Power (Box 393)
          Catalog # MAL 7408; A-side Matrix # MAL 7408 A1A T1
          Jackson, MS
        - Power - Play it again, Sam, 1981; SR-28118; Power (Box 393)
          Catalog # MAL 1204; A-side Matrix # 1T MAL-1204-A-T1
        - Power Cut Crew - Power cut 1, 1988; SR-28119; Power Cut Crew (Box 393)
          Catalog # PC-01; A-side Matrix # PC-001-A MT PA 2854
          Power Cut Records
        - Power Station - Some like it hot and the heat is on, 1985; SR-28120; Power Station (Box 393)
          Catalog # V-8631; A-side Matrix # V-1-8631-600950-Z2
        - Power Station - Communication, 1985; SR-28121; Power Station (Box 393)
          Catalog # V-15204; A-side Matrix # V-1-15204-600954-B.Z2
        - Power Station - Get it on, 1985; SR-28122; Power Station (Box 393)
          Catalog # V-8646; A-side Matrix # V-8646-600955 F-2
        - Powerful - Street life, 1995; SR-28123; Powerful; Hip Hop Junkies (Box 393)
          Catalog # MCT-714; A-side Matrix # MCT-71A 714A AATB
          Mascot Records
        - Powerline - Journey, 1981; SR-28124; Powerline (Box 393)
          Catalog # PRL D 543; A-side Matrix # PRLD-624-AS
        - Powerlords - E-Man EP, 1991; SR-28125; Powerlords (Box 393)
          Catalog # VST 1336; A-side Matrix # VST 1336 A-1 U-1-1
          Virgin
        - Powerlords - E-Man EP, 1991; SR-28126; Powerlords (Box 393)
        - Powers, Will - Smile, 1983; SR-28127; Powers, Will (Box 393)
          In same jacket as # SR-28128. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DMD 674; A-side Matrix # STDM-45364-2
        - Powers, Will - Smile, 1983; SR-28128; Powers, Will (Box 393)
          In same jacket as # SR-28127. 2 copies.
        - Powerule - Smooth, 1989; SR-28129; Powerule (Box 393)
          Catalog # REV 5; A-side Matrix # REV-5 A
          Revenge Records
        - Powerule - Smooth, 1989; SR-28130; Powerule (Box 393)
        - PPK - Resurection, 2002; SR-28141; PPK (Box 393)
          Catalog # TB2358; A-side Matrix # TB-2358 A-1
          Tommy Boy Silver Label
        - Praga Khan - Injected with a poison (digital orgasm remixes), 1992; SR-28131; Praga Khan; Jade 4 U (Box 393)
          Catalog # PROFT 347R; A-side Matrix # PROFT 347R A-1
          Warple Way, London
        - Pras - What'cha wanna do, 1998; SR-28132; Pras; Product G and B; Free (Box 393)
          Catalog # CAS 41727; A-side Matrix # XSS-41727A-1A
        - Pras - Blue angels, 1998; SR-28133; Pras (Box 393)
          Catalog # CAS 41157; A-side Matrix # XSS 41157-2A
        - Pras - One for my n***gaz, 2003; SR-28134; Pras; Sheek (Box 393)
          Catalog # GE1; A-side Matrix # GE1-A RJ
          Guerrilla Entertainment
        - Pras - Ghetto superstar, 1998; SR-28135; Pras (Box 393)
          In same jacket as # SR-28136. 2 copies.
          Catalog # INT8P-6326; A-side Matrix # OASIS DISC MASTERING INT8P-6326A
        - Pras - Ghetto superstar, 1998; SR-28136; Pras (Box 393)
          In same jacket as # SR-28135. 2 copies.
        - Praxis - 1984, 1984; SR-28137; Praxis (Box 393)
          Catalog # CEL 168; A-side Matrix # B-2 CEL 168-A
        - Praxis - Turn me out, 1994; SR-28138; Praxis; Brown, Kathy (Box 393)
          Catalog # CR-295; A-side Matrix # HERBIE JR P.S. ALICIA + AMANDA CR-295-A
          Cutting Records
        - Praxis - 1984, 1984; SR-28139; Praxis (Box 393)
          In same jacket as # SR-28140. 2 copies.
        - Praxis - 1984, 1984; SR-28140; Praxis (Box 393)
          In same jacket as # SR-28139. 2 copies.
        - Praxis - 1984, 1984; SR-28142; Praxis (Box 393)
        - P.R.A.Y. - Mother of my child, 1993; SR-28143; P.R.A.Y. (Box 393)
          Catalog # GAS8P 3112; A-side Matrix # GAS 12033 FDS-1
          Gasoline Alley Records
        - Pregunta - Shangri la, 1978; SR-28144; Pregunta (Box 393)
          Catalog # GNP 12001; A-side Matrix # B-13823
          GNP Crescendo
        - Prelude To Passion - Tempted (to give in), 1987; SR-28145; Prelude To Passion (Box 393)
          Catalog # LA-92086; A-side Matrix # LA-92086-A
          Starrway Records
          New Rochelle, New York
        - Prentiss, Lee - Love this way, 1983; SR-28146; Prentiss, Lee (Box 393)
          In same jacket as # SR-28147. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MSB 12-182; A-side Matrix # MSB-12-1-82-A
          MSB Records, Ltd.
        - Prentiss, Lee - Love this way, 1983; SR-28147; Prentiss, Lee (Box 393)
          In same jacket as # SR-28146. 2 copies. Annotated.
        - Prep MC - I just want to use your love, 1991; SR-28148; Prep MC (Box 394)
          Catalog # PR-E-724; A-side Matrix # RF ST-E-724-A-1 IN GOD WE TRUST
          Effect Records
        - Presley, Elvis - Clambake, 1978; SR-28149; Presley, Elvis (Box 394)
          Catalog # APL1-2565; A-side Matrix # APL1-2565A-1
          RCA Victor
        - Pressure Drop - Elusive (Disc one), 1997; SR-14085; Pressure Drop (Box 394)
          In same jacket as # SR-14086. Double album.
          Catalog # HAND LP3; A-side Matrix # ELUSIVE 01 488525 20 1A1
          Hard Hands
        - Pressure Drop - Elusive (Disc two), 1997; SR-14086; Pressure Drop (Box 394)
          In same jacket as # SR-14085. Double album.
          Catalog # HAND 3LP; A-side Matrix # 01 488525 20 1C1
        - Pressure Drop - For real, 1997; SR-28150; Pressure Drop (Box 394)
          Catalog # HAND43T1; A-side Matrix # HAND 043 TP-A1
        - Presta, Peter "At Work" - Mix of Trixx (part 3), 1995; SR-28151; Presta, Peter "At Work" (Box 394)
          Catalog # CR-346; A-side Matrix # CR-346-A
          Cutting Traxx
        - Presta, Peter "At Work" - Nuttin' but the reel (for yo' hip-hop freaks), 1997; SR-28152; Presta, Peter "At Work" (Box 394)
          Catalog # CR-405; A-side Matrix # CR-405-A
          Cuttin' Hip Hop
        - Preston, Billy - The way I am, 1981; SR-28153; Preston, Billy (Box 394)
          Catalog # M8-941M1; A-side Matrix # M8-941M1A-15D BAS
        - Preston, Billy - The collection (Disc one), 1989; SR-28154; Preston, Billy (Box 394)
          Catalog # CCSLP 210; A-side Matrix # CCSLP 210 A1
          Castle Communications
          Merton Road, London
        - Preston, Billy - The collection (Disc two), 1989; SR-28155; Preston, Billy (Box 394)
          Catalog # CCSLP 210; A-side Matrix # CCSLP 210 C1
        - Preston, Billy - Billy Preston & Syreeta, 1981; SR-28156; Preston, Billy; Syreeta (Box 394)
          Catalog # M8-958 M1; A-side Matrix # PR 85A-66336-D/66336DI-15B ZTK #13 BFL
        - Preston, Billy - I wrote a simple song, 1971; SR-28157; Preston, Billy (Box 394)
          Catalog # SP-3507; A-side Matrix # AMSP 3517 M2 REPL 1704
        - Preston, Billy - And dance; Kick-it, 1984; SR-28158; Preston, Billy (Box 394)
          Catalog # MT-124; A-side Matrix # MT-124-A
        - Preston, Billy - The best, 1982; SR-28159; Preston, Billy (Box 394)
          Catalog # SP-3205; A-side Matrix # AM SP 03205-A ES1
        - Pretenders - Back on the chain gang, 1982; SR-28160; Pretenders (Box 394)
          Catalog # PRO-A-1085; A-side Matrix # 3107 PRO A1-1085-SH1 B-17429-SH1 + SLM
        - Pretty Poison - When I look into your eyes, 1988; SR-28161; Pretty Poison (Box 394)
          Catalog # DMD 1204; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-55433-55434-1 Precision Lacquer JW
        - Pretty Ricky - Grind with me, 2005; SR-28162; Pretty Ricky (Box 394)
          Catalog # PR 301724; A-side Matrix # C.E.J. Rocks!!! ST-PR-301724 A-1
        - Pretty Ricky - Bluestars (Disc one), 2005; SR-28163; Pretty Ricky (Box 394)
          In same jacket as # SR-28164. Double album.
          Catalog # PR 301794; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301794A-1 RJ
        - Pretty Ricky - Bluestars (Disc two), 2005; SR-28164; Pretty Ricky (Box 394)
          In same jacket as # SR-28163. Double album.
          Catalog # PR 301794; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301794C-2 RJ
        - Pretty Ricky - Bluestars (Disc one), 2005; SR-28165; Pretty Ricky (Box 394)
          In same jacket as # SR-28166. Double album.
          Catalog # 83786-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-83786A-1 RJ
        - Pretty Ricky - Bluestars (Disc two), 2005; SR-28166; Pretty Ricky (Box 394)
          In same jacket as # SR-28165. Double album.
          Catalog # 83786-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-83786C-1 RJ
        - Pretty Ricky - Your body, 2005; SR-28167; Pretty Ricky (Box 394)
          Catalog # PR 301868; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301868A-1 RJ
        - Pretty Ricky - Your body, 2005; SR-28168; Pretty Ricky (Box 394)
        - Pretty Ricky - Grind with me, 2005; SR-28169; Pretty Ricky (Box 394)
        - Pretty Ricky - Nothing but a number; Call me, 2005; SR-28170; Pretty Ricky (Box 394)
          Catalog # PR 302054; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-302054A-1 RT
        - Pretty Ricky - It's mine, 1985; SR-28171; Pretty Ricky; Boo-Ski (Box 394)
          Catalog # FMS 62268; A-side Matrix # FMS-62268-A
        - Pretty Tony - Fix it in the mix, 1984; SR-28172; Pretty Tony (Box 394)
          Catalog # MSI-104; A-side Matrix # C-1 MSI-104-A
          Music Specialists
        - Pretty Tony - Down in tha dirty; Superman, 2003; SR-28173; Pretty Tony (Box 394)
          Catalog # 82876-52947-1; A-side Matrix # 82876-52947-1SA RT
          J Records
        - Pretty Tony - Down in tha dirty; Superman, 2003; SR-28174; Pretty Tony (Box 394)
        - Pretzel's Logic - The promo, 1995; SR-28175; Pretzel's Logic (Box 394)
          Catalog # 1368-1215; A-side Matrix # 1368-1215-A
          Domestic Violence Entertainment
        - Price, Kelly - Secret love, 1997; SR-28176; Price, Kelly (Box 394)
          Catalog # 314-572 611-1; A-side Matrix # PR12 7997-1 A
        - Price, Kelly - You should've told me, 2000; SR-28177; Price, Kelly (Box 394)
          Catalog # 314 562 954-1; A-side Matrix # 314 562 954-1 DEFR 15142-1A
          Def Soul
        - Price, Kelly - Friend of mine, 1998; SR-28178; Price, Kelly (Box 394)
          Catalog # 314-572 331-1DJ; A-side Matrix # 314-572 331-1 A -HS
        - Price, Kelly - Friend of mine, 1998; SR-28179; Price, Kelly (Box 394)
        - Price, Kelly - Love sets you free, 2000; SR-28180; Price, Kelly (Box 394)
          Catalog # DEFR 15039-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR15039-1-A-R-1
        - Price, Kelly - Love sets you free, 2000; SR-28192; Price, Kelly; Friends (Box 394)
          Catalog # 314 562 701-1; A-side Matrix # 314562701-1-A
        - Price, Sean - Boom bye yeah; 60 bar dash, 2005; SR-28181; Price, Sean (Box 394)
          Catalog # DDM-SI-3006; A-side Matrix # DDM-SI-3006-A
          Duck Down
        - Pride 'N Politix - Hold on, 1991; SR-28182; Pride 'N Politix (Box 394)
          Catalog # A8707T; A-side Matrix # A8707T A1 SAM-872-A-1
          EastWest
        - Priest - Untitled, 1998; SR-28183; Priest; Eddie Lock & The SMC Project (Box 394)
          Catalog # PS030; A-side Matrix # PS 30 A1
          Plastic Surgery
          Maidstone, England
        - Priest - Iceolation (too cold too hot), 1997; SR-28184; Priest (Box 394)
          Catalog # PS 029; A-side Matrix # PS-029-A1
        - Priest, Maxi - Just a little bit longer, 1990; SR-28185; Priest, Maxi (Box 394)